{
    "subject": "resource/Frederick_Valentine_Melsheimer",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1749_births",
    "human_readable": "Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's subject category is 1749 births.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8056179285049438,
            "question": "In what year was Frederick Valentine Melsheimer born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7563046813011169,
            "question": "What category does Frederick Valentine Melsheimer belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6324971318244934,
            "question": "Are there any primary sources about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5547139644622803,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people born in 1749?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5415104031562805,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about people born in 1749?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4933132231235504,
            "question": "Who are some other notable figures from the year 1749?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42997634410858154,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4099872410297394,
            "question": "What historical events occurred during Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3596760630607605,
            "question": "What impact did Frederick Valentine Melsheimer have on his time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24020981788635254,
            "question": "What is the significance of categorizing individuals by birth year?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's subject category is 1749 births.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5224_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Frederick Valentine Melsheimer have on his time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5224_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical events occurred during Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5224_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can we learn more about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5224_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5224_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer, and it is mentioned that he was born in 1749. Therefore, the triple \"Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's subject category is 1749 births\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer, including his birth date of September 25, 1749. Therefore, the statement that his subject category is 1749 births is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}